https://www.wsd.org.uk/privacy-policy-may-2018

Privacy Statement
Preservation of your privacy is important to the Association of Guilds of Weavers, Spinners and Dyers (AGWSD) and we are committed to letting you know how we use your personal information and to making only responsible use of your data.
References to “we”, “us”, “you” or “our” in this Privacy Policy are references to the AGWSD (a charity registered in England and Wales, registered charity number: 289590.)
Information about you
1.1 The AGWSD Secretary will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us.
1.2 We will collect personal information from you when you enquire about our activities, register as a member with us or register for a workshop/course/conference with us. This may include your name, title, email address, physical address and telephone numbers.  We may also ask for some additional, non-personal information.
1.3 We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with on-going organisational updates and information in line with the aims of AGWSD. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need.
Our use of this information
2.1   Your personal information will only be used to process your requests. All the personal data we process is processed by General Purposes Committee as needed. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data.
Security
3.1   We will take all reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information you give us. We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data
3.2   Your information will be retained by us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive any information and/or are no longer a member.
Cookies
4.1   If cookies are used they will only be used to assist the purposes set out in this privacy policy, but cookies will not be used if we do not consider them to be necessary.
Other information
5.1   If you would like us to correct or update any information, or if you would like information deleted from our records, then please email us at secretary@wsd.org.uk
5.2   This privacy policy may be updated from time to time, so please check it periodically.
5.3   Links within our sites to other websites are not covered by this privacy policy.
5.4 If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated.
This Policy was updated May 2018
AGWSD Privacy Statement
Recent Posts
Newsletter September 2020
Newsletter July/August 2020
Newsletter June 2020
Newsletter April 2020
Message From Our Acting Chair – Janet Crowther
Our website use cookies. Learn more about our cookies here. By continuing, you agree to their use. I agree
